I'm glad I got a chance to meet you.
Who knew the money moving around
the crown princess was so fishy?
I see why you're comptroller
of the treasury, assistant or not.
Please, I'm in your debt for all
you've been so good as to tell me.
I hope I'll be seeing more
of you, Rufus May.
Well?
As you suspected, it would appear...
Aldous Clayton is on his way
to interview her.
My mistress's room is
at the end of the hall.
I've made certain you'll have privacy.
Aisha Huxley...
What made her decide to confess
a decade-old crime now?
Oh, but she isn't the quarry
you're after, is she...
Deborah Darkian?
I've made certain you'll have privacy.
Damn and blast!
Hey, you!
He took... the medicine bottle.
Salvador of Daeg Gallus...
She must mean that man.
Sharon... Investigate my cousin Sharon...
I will. Anything else?
Scarlett...
Do you think Scarlett will... forgive me?
Sure she will.
Thank good—
A guard dog's disgrace is
his owner's responsibility, no?
M-Murderer!
Goodbye...
Abigail O'Brian.
What's a wanted murderer doing here?!
Somebody else killed her.
I just got framed.
What an unbelievably stupid dog you are!
You could have at least
been smarter about it!
I'm telling you, I didn't do it.
Don't make excuses!
That attitude is why you slip up,
you mangy stray!
Listen to me, you old hag!
So, um, who might this be?
That's Lady Audrey, our teacher.
She teaches us how to do
our makeup and pick out dresses.
And how to wrap gentlemen
around our fingers!
Wrap them...?
Oh, you're darling.
It's all right if you don't understand.
How long do you intend
to sit around chattering?!
Why must everyone Abigail
brings me be such utter...
What does Abby have to do with it?
I'll have you know the former Duke O'Brian
charged me with guarding this place.
I'll toss lazy layabouts out on their ear!
Enough, silly.
Hey.
Look on the bottom right.
This is Sharon Spencer, Aisha's cousin.
It looks like she died on the same day.
They say it was suicide,
but I'll bet she was murdered.
Daeg Gallus again...
They work fast.
There must be some secret
they really don't want to come out.
Pardon me.
Your Lordship?
My! Here to collect her again?
I need you to listen calmly.
Abigail has been arrested
on suspicion of Aisha Huxley's murder.
There was an anonymous tip.
It said the fugitive Aldous Clayton is
none other than Folkvangr's bouncer, Rudy,
and that it was Abigail
who provided him with his false identity.
Abby...
She's therefore being investigated
for masterminding Aisha's murder.
B-But Lady Abigail had
nothing to do with Aisha!
Abigail wrote to Aisha a week ago.
I'll see to it that you receive
an invitation from the Huxleys soon.
This is my fault...
No, Connie. You did nothing wrong.
I need to do something!
I'll turn myself in.
W-Wait a moment!
Move!
I will not. Giving yourself up
won't save Abby in your place.
Then what am I supposed to do?!
We're going to think of something!
Right now! All of us together!
Connie.
It is true that we have
our own way of doing things.
Do you have an idea?
First, isn't there something
you forgot to say?
Help me, Scarlett!
Oh, very well.
I shall save you.
Naturally, since the charges are false,
they have no evidence
to definitively prove Abigail's guilt.
Our enemies will send a judge
in their pocket for her trial.
Earl Kalvin Campbell
is set to try the case.
In a word, he's a womanizer.
Your quintessential scumbag
who's fathered children all over.
A judge like that is bound
to have dirty secrets.
So...
We find out what they are first
and blackmail him ourselves!
Blackmail?
In that case...
call courtesans to the Earl John Doe Ball
for some drunken merrymaking!
Earl Campbell will leap at
the novel entertainment! It's perfect!
No one can think up
tasteless spectacles quite like you.
I see.
It's an interesting plan.
Give the signal if the worst happens.
I'll threaten him myself.
Thank you, Connie.
For giving us a chance to repay Abby.
Until a few years ago, Rebekah and I were
forced to work somewhere truly awful.
It was practically a prison.
Even if we'd escaped,
we had nowhere to go.
They treated us like slaves.
And then, along came Abby.
I've bought every girl in this place.
Now, let's get out of here.
That's how Abby rescued
all of the girls working here.
So...
So, please, do whatever you can for her.
O-Oh, please raise your heads.
Go on now. Before Audrey catches on.
Before who does what?
Why, Audrey...
Planning how to get out
of work, are you?!
I don't recall teaching you that!
This is the problem with
the lot of you Abigail brought in.
You hardly pass for
decent funeral flowers.
Abby isn't dead yet!
It's too soon for you to be so senile,
you rotten old hag.
"Rotten" is unfair.
She's a perfectly respectable old hag.
Oh, am I?!
I see you girls are
as foul-mouthed as ever.
Laura, go take down the sign.
Don't we have a big party to attend?
We'll close shop for tonight
and focus on cultivating new clientele.
Go make yourselves up! All of you!
Audrey...
What Abigail brings on herself
is no business of mine.
But when they strike at her,
they pick a fight with Folkvangr.
Listen up, girls!
Use every trick in the book
to take this man for all he's worth.
Don't leave a solid bone in his body.
Why?
I did my hair for today!
I had my mask specially made!
So why?!
Why doesn't anyone choose me?!
That's...
the pride of Folkvangr,
Miriam the rose fairy!
My lady.
I beg your pardon.
She's here with me.
She simply won't have
anyone else. Excuse us.
I lost to a man like that?!
Who are you?!
M-My sincere apologies.
Oh, dear me.
The beautiful moon has
shrouded herself in clouds.
Has something happened to sadden you so?
No. At least, nothing I'd dare
to speak of here.
Might I become the wind
to blow your clouds away?
Perhaps you've heard that the owner
of our establishment is under arrest.
When I think that I may
end up on the street,
I find myself overwhelmed with worry.
Does she mean Abigail O'Brian?
I thought it would be a boring job
just delivering a predetermined verdict,
but what an unexpected perk.
When that time comes, call on me.
I'm Kalvin Campbell.
I promise you a comfortable life.
To tell the truth, I've received
a similar offer from Viscount Hamsworth.
Please excuse me.
It's quite true.
Oh, you beast.
Wait! I'll double his offer!
I have all the money you could want!
It's true!
And may I ask... where?
Ill-gotten funds?
He operates hospitals
and orphanages, you know?
The country sponsors this, and he pockets
some of the money on the sly.
Don't worry! The money's clean on paper.
I pool it in the secret accounts
of a citizen's group as "donations"!
We're lucky he's so loose-lipped.
His tiny brain must be
as loose as his pants.
So, um, what citizens' group is this?
It's called the Violet Association.
My, what a coincidence.
O-Oh! That woman all in pink is...
Kimberly Smith of the Violet Association.
And who might you be
to take me aside so abruptly?
I am called "Miss C."
Oh, goodness me. What can I do for you?
What is your relationship
with Earl Kalvin Campbell?
The earl? He's a magnificent gentleman.
He sympathizes with our cause
despite his aristocratic origins.
And donates to it?
How grim you look.
Donating to a cause is hardly a crime.
Indeed, unless the money
was obtained illegally.
What do you mean?
I hear your association
keeps secret accounts.
I take it she genuinely
doesn't know about them.
Tell me,
did the earl tell you that?
I see. The rat is probably...
in our youth committee, I suppose.
How dare he use a defenseless
citizens' group as cover.
That Campbell boy has nerve,
I'll give him that.
By the by,
I suppose you plan to blackmail him
into acquitting Abigail?
To think a "sincere" Grail
would fight fire with fire!
Well, I can't say it's a bad plan.
But you're not quite up to the task.
Very well. I owe you for telling me
about the secret accounts,
so let me take it from here.
What do you mean?
We don't want to see the O'Brians
overthrown any more than you do.
We didn't spend ten years weakening the
Darkians only to watch them rise again.
Just who is this woman?
You can't trust me?
Then I'll give you a little hint.
What color are violets?
Our country's violets
have an unusual reddish hue.
It has come to represent the royal family
because it matches their eyes.
The royals of Faris, on the other hand,
have bluish-purple eyes.
In both Adelbide and Faris,
these eye colors symbolize their royalty.
Which would suggest the Violet Association
that Kimberly belongs to is...
What are you doing?
It's almost time for the verdict.
Do you think she'll be all right?
That depends on Kimberly Smith.
Lady Abigail...
Miss Grail?
Your Lordship!
How did it go?
What was the verdict?!
Not guilty.
Due to insufficient evidence.
Although...
the earl looked as if he'd been
sentenced to death when he delivered it.
It seems that woman managed well enough.
Abigail will be released as soon
as the formalities are taken care of.
Th-Thank goodness!
Oh no. I feel faint.
Are you all right?
So close...
He's so, so, so close!
Oh, his chest sure is firm...
Wait, no! I mean, this is... I know!
This is a kind of a rescue effort!
Certainly not a lover's embrace or...
Your face is flushed.
Do you have a fever or—
N-N-Not at all! I'm quite well!
Yes, yes. That's enough of that.
Abby!
I... wasn't the least bit worried for you!
Lucia...
After that...
once news of Lady Abigail's
innocence spread,
the search for the true culprit
led to the arrest of a suitable man,
who confessed to Aisha's murder
and took his own life that evening.
Meanwhile,
an accusation started doing the rounds.
It claimed someone had leaked information
about Aisha which had to her murder.
And that someone...
was Amelia Hobbes.
Crown Princess Cecilia!
Who're you? And who are you
calling "crown princess"?
You can't fool me.
Word has spread, and no publisher
will give me the time of day now!
To make my comeback,
I need a scandal that no one can deny!
You need what?
Cici.
Almost every other child
in your old orphanage died in a fire.
Only two remain unaccounted for.
You and that boy, Cici—
Cici is dead.
Do you want to die too?
Then disappear from this country
before the day is out.
If you don't,
I'll dye that shabby red hair
of yours a lovely crimson.
What are you racking
your inadequate brain over?
You're awful!
I've told you, your face gives you away.
Remember what Abigail said?
Connie, you'd better watch out yourself.
This was too smoothly done to be
a cover-up of a decade-old crime.
Something tells me there's yet
a big secret we don't know.
Daeg Gallus is hunting
for Lady Lily's key.
So if we solve the mystery of that key
and the phrase "the Holy Grail of Eris,"
it may give us a clue.
Hello there,
charming young lady.
I'm looking for the Grand Merillian.
Might I ask you the way?
O-Of course. It's just—
San!
Oh, Eularia.
I looked everywhere for you! Honestly!
You lose your way at the drop of a hat!
Me? Surely it was you who lost your way.
Yes, yes. I'm sure that's
how it seems to you!
Now, please, at least carry a map.
See this?
You take the letters
and number written here
and use them to...
That's a large bundle on her back.
What could it be?
I see. That does seem convenient.
Doesn't it just?
Now you won't get lost any—
Here. For you.
I never get lost, you see.
I beg your pardon?!
I'm San. May I ask your name?
I'm C-Constance Grail.
Grail? Why...
What a lovely name.
W-Wait for me, San!
Listen until I'm done talking to you!
Honestly! Why must you always...
Lady Lily's key!
This is no key.
I tracked down where it was made.
It's merely a key-shaped decoration.
However,
this inscription was added
at Lily's express direction.
P10E3...
What is it?
Excuse me for a moment!
What's come over you?
Scarlett...
I think I might have figured it out.
A BANQUET OF INSECTIVOROUS PLANTS
Translation:
William Varteresian
Subtitle Timing:
Edgar Cruz
Subtitle Editing:
Riley Dalton
Quality Check:
SMR
Translation Check:
Sriram Gurunathan